redroom.com 2008-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Red Room

Red Room Omnimedia Corporation regards your online privacy as an important and serious matter. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to this issue. As we at Red Room continue to develop our online enterprises, we may add new features, change the type of information we gather, or the method by which it is gathered. We will adjust this privacy policy to reflect any changes, and notify users of any personal information we are requesting. Please review this policy for changes from time to time, and contact us if you have any questions. Red Room may change this policy occasionally at its discretion. Your continued use of our site indicates your consent to this privacy policy and any amended versions of it. This policy was last updated on May 26th, 2007.

**California and Canadian Users:** California and Canadian residents have the right to know how their information may be shared with third parties who engage in direct marketing activities, and this policy explains our practices and how you can opt out of having your information shared for such purposes. We will not share your personal information to third parties, although from time to time we may ask your permission to do so with companies whose products or services we believe would be of interest to you. 

**IP addresses:** An IP address is a number assigned to the computer which is requesting a page from our site. Usually, it is not your personal computer, but a computer used by your internet service provider or company network. Red Room uses IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website, and to report aggregate information. 

**The information we collect includes:** The IP address of the computer making the request, the URL that is being requested, the date and time of the request, the referring URL, and the browser type and operating system used to make the request. 

**Cookies:** A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help target Web ads based on user behavior—for example, to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to remember certain actions you take, such as logging in to one of our services, or remembering a set of search results you requested. Most Web browsers will allow you to adjust your cookie settings. However, some of our online services will not work if you disable our ability to set cookies. 

**Registration:** Red Room requires registration for certain features on redroom.com. Red Room does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 and wish to use this site please inform us so that we can comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The Red Room registration form requires users to provide a name, an email address, approximate age, gender, and ZIP code. After registering, you may receive communications from redroom.com regarding Red Room products, services, and programs. You can change this choice at any time by logging in to your account and checking/unchecking the correct box at the “My Account” link. 

**Newsletters:** Registration is required when signing up for our online newsletters. 

**Email to a friend:** Red Room offers you the ability to easily email information from our site to your friends. 

**Third-party advertising and content:** Red Room has partnerships with other companies and links to other websites. If you choose to visit and/or use the services provided by those sites, you may be asked by those sites to provide certain personally identifiable information. Some of this information may, on an individual or aggregated basis, be shared with us. However, we will keep any individually identifiable information private unless otherwise stated at the location where the information is requested. Please be aware that Red Room is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites, even if our name or logo may appear on those sites (a.k.a. "co-branded"). Third party websites may appear in a new window, or they may appear in a frame. If frames are used, you may still see our site’s URL in the address window, but you are actually on another website. In most cases, any third party page, even in a frame, is branded with the third party’s name. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and read the Privacy Statements of each and every website that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our privacy policy applies solely to Red Room. 

**Public forums:** This site makes certain features, such as blogs and groups, available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security:** Although no system can be guaranteed to be completely secure, Red Room endeavors to make our website safe. Security measures are in place and designed to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Illegal activity:** Red Room may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or at our discretion in order to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without prior notice to you. Red Room reserves the right to share personally identifiable information to cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. 

**Sharing information:** In addition to the other situations described in this policy, and notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, Red Room may also share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when: 

• We utilize third party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf (such as sending emails, processing credit cards, fulfilling subscriptions or performing statistical analysis about site usage), and ask these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and not to use your personally identifiable information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them;

• the entity to whom the information is disclosed is one under control of, or under common control with Red Room (for these purposes, a company controlling 20 percent or more of the voting stock of another entity shall be deemed to control such entity);

• we need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us); 

• we must comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal or regulatory process; or 

• in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (whether of assets, stock, or otherwise) of all or a portion of the business conducted by the websites to which this policy applies. 

**Non-U.S. users:** If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this website, you consent to this transfer. You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with this website in the federal and state courts of, and in accordance with the laws of, California, United States in which the editorial staff of this website primarily does business. 

**Contact:** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us.
